Part 1 dataset (Lizard) can be found at:
https://warwick.ac.uk/fac/cross_fac/tia/data/lizard

Part 2 and Part 3 datasets are not public. The source data can be found at the VGG NAS.

It is recommended you download the version of this folder from:
https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1TGvgrrHHlmc_ZDcsXUfNVSgYyIP9KpgP?usp=sharing
To run our solutions as described. If you decide to use the version submitted to AIS, you have to download
at least the data folders from Google Drive and place the data in paths described in Appendix F